‘It’s good to talk’, so some people say.
有人说，“交流是件好事”。
When I commute into London, there are certainly plenty of people conversing on their mobile phones – sometimes too loudly – discussing and sharing personal details with a friend.
当我通勤去伦敦时，确实有很多人在手机上聊天——有时声音太大了——和朋友讨论、分享个人琐事。
For me, it’s strange that they talk as though the person is sitting next to them, when they don’t even acknowledge the person who is actually sitting beside them.
对我来说，奇怪的是，他们聊天时仿佛对方就坐在身边，却对真正坐在旁边的人视而不见。
Many of us spend part of each day surrounded by strangers, whether on our daily commute, or sitting in a park or a cafe.
我们很多人每天都会有一部分时间被陌生人包围，无论是日常通勤时，还是坐在公园或咖啡馆里。
But most of them remain just that – strangers.
但大多数人终究只是陌生人。
However, new evidence has shown that plucking up the courage to strike up a conversation might be good for our health.
不过，新的证据表明，鼓起勇气主动搭话可能对我们的健康有益。
Nicholas Epley from the University of Chicago and Juliana Schroeder from the University of California are behavioural scientists.
芝加哥大学的尼古拉斯·埃普利和加州大学的朱莉安娜·施罗德是行为科学家。
They looked at this silent relationship and whether solitude is a more positive experience than interacting with strangers, or if people misunderstand the consequences of distant social connections.
他们研究了这种“沉默的关系”，探究独处是否比与陌生人互动更积极，以及人们是否误解了疏远的社交关系所带来的影响。
They found that many people feel uncomfortable and intimidated talking to others and their research suggested that when we make an initial conversation “we consistently underestimate how much a new person likes us.”
他们发现，很多人在与他人交谈时会感到不适和胆怯，而他们的研究表明，当我们主动开启第一次对话时，“我们总是低估陌生人对我们的好感度”。
It seems we carry a negative voice in our head telling us all the things that could go wrong and why someone wouldn’t want to converse with us.
似乎我们脑海里总有一个负面的声音，告诉我们所有可能出错的事情，以及别人为什么不想和我们交谈。
Their research involved an experiment with a group of Chicago commuters and found that “every participant in our experiment who actually tried to talk to a stranger found the person sitting next to them was happy to chat.”
他们的研究包括一项针对芝加哥通勤者的实验，结果是“实验中每一个真正尝试与陌生人交谈的参与者，都发现坐在身边的人很乐意聊天”。
From this and other research, the conclusion is that connecting with strangers is surprisingly pleasant and it has a positive impact on our wellbeing.
从这项研究和其他研究中得出的结论是，与陌生人交流令人意外地愉快，并且对我们的身心健康有积极影响。
Gillian Sandstrom, a social psychologist from Essex University in the UK, told the BBC that “people are in a better mood after they reach out and have a conversation, however minimal.”
英国埃塞克斯大学的社会心理学家吉莉安·桑德斯特伦向英国广播公司表示：“当人们主动进行交谈时，无论对话多么简短，他们的心情都会变得更好。”
It’s true that talking can make you feel happier and happiness can lead to better mental health.
的确，交谈能让你感到更快乐，而快乐有助于提升心理健康水平。
However, if you’re an introvert, the thought of speaking to someone new might make you anxious.
但如果你是一个内向的人，一想到要和陌生人说话，可能就会感到焦虑。
But the American research found “both extroverts and introverts are happier when they are asked to behave in an extroverted manner.”
不过这项美国研究发现，“无论是外向者还是内向者，当他们尝试以更外向的方式行事时，都会感到更快乐”。
So maybe, if you’re a loner, it’s time to come out of your shell and make some small talk with a stranger – it could be the beginning of a new friendship.
所以，如果你是一个喜欢独处的人，或许是时候敞开心扉，和陌生人聊几句闲话了——这或许会成为一段新友谊的开端。